<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="cam_header">Here To Help!</string>
    <string name="gif_space_header">Here To Help!</string>

    <string name="cam_intro_1">
        Thank you for trying GifIt!\nYou can close this window and come back to it any time by
        clicking the Gears icon on the right of the screen:
    </string>
    <string name="cam_intro_2"> This is a brief overview of what you can do with it. </string>
    <string name="cam_summary_1">
        You can do 3 things with GifIt:\n
        1. Snap Gifs\n
        2. Customize Gifs\n
        3. Share Gifs\n
        4. Swipe left or right to switch between the Camera and the Gif view.
    </string>
    <string name="cam_summary_2">
        The app currently consists of 2 tabs. You flip between your camera
        and your workspace by swiping left and right. Your workspace tab appears once you have
        created a gif but your camera tab always persists.
    </string>
    <string name="ad_shade_snippet">
        Ad Shade: Ads are important in supporting this pro-bono app, but some
        can get irritating when they try too hard to grab your attention. If that is the case,
        simply tap the ad shade button and it slides an opaque screen around the ad. You can still
        see a little bit of the ad and can still click it if you want to.
    </string>
    <string name="shutter_snippet">
        Shutter Button: Like the button on your camera but a lil
        different. Press it once and your gif will start capturing. You will see its progress with 
        the red progress bar circling the button. You can interrupt the capture by pressing it once
        again while the capture is running. Once it is done capturing the Gif frames, the app will 
        flip to the gif workspace and build your gif once it is done capturing.
    </string>
    <string name="frame_rate_snippet">
        Frame Rate Scroller: Set the gif camera frames per second (scroll up or down). Set how fast
        you want to capture gif frames. A higher value means a smoother gif, but also a shorter
        time frame overall for your gif, because the number of frames you can take is limited.
    </string>
    <string name="frame_count_snippet">
        Frame Count Scroller: Set the number of frames to take for your gif. Around 6 is good. Going over 10 frames will
        start taking a little while longer to render your Gifs.
    </string>
    <string name="shutter_sound_snippet">
        Shutter Sound Toggle: Turn the rapid shot camera shutter sound on or off.
    </string>
    <string name="flip_cam_snippet">
        Flip Camera: Flip between your phone\'s front and back facing cameras.
    </string>
    <string name="set_flash_snippet">
        Set Flash: Set the flash mode for your camera. Please be aware that because of the way we have this app
        set up capturing rapid frames, some phones may only have limited flash modes and for some
        the flash may not function at all. We still chose to keep this feature because it will work
        for some of you!
    </string>
    <string name="T_snippet">
        Add Text: Open a text box and add text to your Gif! Hit the check button that appears to update your
        Gif with the change
    </string>
    <string name="share_snippet">
        Share: Share your Gif! with friends! Opens up a sharing menu where you can pick your sharing method
        of choice, Flicking upwards on your Gif will also do this. You Gifs are only saved when they
        are shared - we would not want to fill up your phone with junk you do not intend to keep.
    </string>
    <string name="glove_snippet">
        Move, Rotate, Resize: This glove indicates that the current resource on the screen can be moved, rotated, and
        resized. It goes away after you click it or when you click the image resource in question.
    </string>
    <string name="check_snippet">
        Check Button: Confirm changes and reload your Gif. When you see this, it means that you
        probably made some changes to your Gif and hitting this button will update the gif image
        with the changes. You could have added some text, removed some unwanted frames, or changed
        the gif speed. Click on this button to save your changes and reload the Gif!
    </string>
    <string name="gif_speed_slider_snippet">
        Change Gif Speed: Use this slider to change the speed of the gif you just created. Gif speed refers to how
        fast the image frames change from one to another. Move it to the right to speed the Gif up
        and move it to the left to slow the Gif down.The changes cannot be made in real time and the
        Gif needs to be reloaded for the changes to take effect. Click on the round check button
        that appears after you move the slider to reload the gif and check out how fast it is now!
    </string>
    <string name="frames_snippet">
        Editing Gif Frames: When you create your gif, at the bottom of the screen you will see all
        of the image frames included in that Gif. You can add and remove these frames as you wish to
        tune your Gif to your liking. Simply click on a frame and you will see a red X over it. Then
        click the check button that should have appeared and your Gif will be recreated with the
        chosen frame removed. You can remove all but 1 frame. You can also add back frames that have
        been removed if you change your mind. Simply click the frame that has a red X over it that
        you wish to add back and then reload the Gif using the check button. Your Gif will be
        reloaded with the chosen frame present.
    </string>

    <string name="help_outro_1_1"> Please Email us at </string>
    <string name="help_outro_1_2"> codewrencher@gmail.com </string>
    <string name="help_outro_1_3"> with any comments / concerns / suggestions </string>

    <string name="help_outro_2_1"> Please visit </string>
    <string name="help_outro_2_2"> www.CodeWrencher.com </string>
    <string name="help_outro_2_3"> for more apps and info! </string>

</resources>